Guide to the Lee Felsenstein Papers M1443
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Lee Felsenstein papers
circa 1975-2007
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Felsenstein, Lee.
M1443
56 Linear Feet
The papers of computer designer Lee Felsenstein contain material about the development of personal computers through the 1970s and 80s.
Biographical / Historical
Lee Felsenstein is an electronic design engineer known for his contributions to the early history of personal computing. Born in Philadelphia, PA in 1945, Felsenstein studied electrical engineering and computer science at the University of California, Berkeley, where he took part in the 1964 Free Speech Movement protests and was employed as a junior engineer at Ampex. Working as a contract engineer since the 1970’s, much of Felsenstein’s output has focused on making personal computing more publicly accessible. His contributions to the history of computing include designing the 1973 Pennywhistle modem, an early acoustic coupler modem affordable to hobbyists, and the Osborne 1, the first commercially successful portable computer, released by the Osborne Computer Corporation in 1981. Additionally, Felsenstein is known for co-founding the Community Memory Project, a publicly-accessible computer bulletin board system self-branded as an “information flea market,” in 1973, and for his role from 1975 to 1986 as moderator of the Homebrew Computer Club, a Silicon Valley-based group of computing enthusiasts whose membership included Bob Marsh, Steve Wozniak, Adam Osborne, and Jerry Lawson, among others.
Felsenstein also designed Processor Technology’s SOL-20 microcomputer, a popular hobbyist’s computer terminal released in 1976, and the VDM-1, an inexpensive video display module that served as a blueprint for the architecture of personal computing, released in 1975. Felsenstein has additionally engaged in nonprofit efforts such as the Jhai PC, a ‘remote village IT system’ designed for usage in rural jungle environments in Laos, and the Free Speech Movement Archives, an online hub for information related to the 1964-1965 Berkeley protests that Felsenstein himself took part in.
In 1994, the Electronic Frontier Foundation awarded Lee Felsenstein a Pioneer Award for his contributions to personal computing. He was made a laureate of the Tech Museum of Innovation in 2003, and was made a Fellow of the Computer History Museum in 2016 “for his influence on the technical and social environment of the early personal computing era”.
Scope and Contents
Material was rehoused and listed by box. Series were created after the fact and descriptions rearranged for readability.
The collection is arranged in eight series:
Series 1: Community Memory Project Series 2: Golemics Series 3: Homebrew Computer Club Series 4: LGC Engineering Series 5: Osborn Computer Corporation Series 6: Village Design Series 7: Upstart Corporation Series 8: Accession 2017-243
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research except for Series I: Community Memory Project, Subseries 1.6: Payroll, which is closed until Jan. 1, 2060. Computer media is also closed until processed. Note that material must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection was given by Lee Felsenstein to Stanford University, Special Collections in 2004 and 2017.
Science -- History.; Computer industry -- United States -- History; Felsenstein, Lee.; Homebrew Computer Club; Community Memory Project (Calif.); Golemics (Firm)
- Series 1: Community Memory Project
  Conditions Governing Access
  Subseries 1.6: Payroll is closed until Jan. 1, 2060.
  - Subseries 1.1: Receipts
    - Community Memory Project check receipts, Dec. 1991 - Dec. 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Office Expenses (P.O. Box rental), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Public Storage, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Employee Reimbursement, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Office Supplies, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Petty Cash Information, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - US Postmaster, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - CoinBox, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Check Register, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Check Register, 1993 - 1995 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - CD Rom and other orders paid by Mastercard and Visa, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Scope and Contents
      Materials pertaining to Sequitur (trademark of The Community Memory Project), a relational database system.
    - SEQB12-Advance Support Payments, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Consulting, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Employee Reimbursements, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Health Insurance, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 1.2: Invoices
    - Electronic Mail: service from Institute for Global Communications, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Insurance: invoices regarding insurance, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Pacific Bell, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
    - Copies: service from Kinko's, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Electronic Mail: service from Institute for Global Communications, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Inkworks, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Newsletter: service from Cerebral Palsy Center for Bay Area, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Pacific Gas and Electric, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Pacific Bell, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 21-22)
    - Professional Services: service from Christy Bertani Bookkeeping, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Public Storage, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Red Alarm, Inc., 1992 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Requests of UC: timesheets and invoices for college work/study program, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Insurance Policies, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Electronic Mail and Internet Service Provider: service from Institute for Global Communications; Netcom, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Insurance, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Pacific Bell, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Electronic Mail and Internet Service Provider: service from Institute for Global Communications; Netcom, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Insurance, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Pacific Bell, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Working Assets, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Electronic Mail: service from Institute for Global Communications, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Pacific Bell, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 22-23)
    - Reimbursements: contains receipts, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - In Process, 1991-2000 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Sequitur-Invoice Master File, 1984-1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Sequitur-blank invoices (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Sequitur-Memo Billing, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - CD Rom mailing list orders, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Sequitur-open accounts receivable, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Sequitur-closed accounts receivable, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Sequitur-closed accounts receivable 4500-4600, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Sequitur-closed accounts receivable 6700-5596 (new series), 1986 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Sequitur-closed accounts receivable 0500-0600, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Sequiter Pacific Software Royalties, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Posted Expenses, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Cash Disbursements Bills, August 1990 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Cash Disbursements Bills, September 1990 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Cash Disbursements Bills, October 1990 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Cash Disbursements Bills, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 30-31)
    - Advertising/Promotion, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Copies, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Domino Computer, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Education, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Electronic Mail: Wells/Peacnet, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Inkworks, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Ins Biz Gen, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Ed Kirwin Graphics, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Legal, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - MCI, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Misc. Computer, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Misc. Newsletters, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Office Supplies, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Oz-Cleaning, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - CRJ Check Stubs, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - PG&E, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Red Alarm, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Rent-T. Maggio, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - SF Chronicle, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Subscriptions, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - UC Regents, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - US Postmaster, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - PacBell, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 38-40)
  - Subseries 1.3: Taxes
    - Licenses, Taxes, Registration: paperwork regarding business license; status as a non-profit, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 990 and Schedule A, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 199, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - CT-2, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Licenses, Taxes, Registration: paperwork regarding business license; status as a non-profit, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 199, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - CT-2, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 990, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Taxes Amended 1988 and 1989 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Office Expenses; Business License; Property Taxes, etc., 1996 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - 990; 199; 8734 Schedule, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Office Expenses; Business License; Property Taxes, etc., 1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 990; 199; CT-2, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Insurance: includes correspondence, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Licenses, Taxes, Registration: paperwork regarding business license; status as a non-profit, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Office Expenses: service from You Send Me, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 990; 199; CT-2, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 990, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - 941, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - DE3, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - 940 Yearly Return, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - 1096 + 1099 Misc, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Statement by Domestic NP Corp, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - W-2 + W-3, DE43, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Amended 990, 199, CT-2, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - 199, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - CT-2, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - 941, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - DE3, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - 940, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - W-2 On File, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Stmt Domestic Nonprofit, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - W-2 Filled Out, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Registration, Licenses + Taxes, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - State Comp Ins Work Comp, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Subseries 1.4: Correspondence
    - MCI: information about account, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Information: notices; letter, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous: contains marketing outline; notes on pilot project; scholarly papers, 1983-2000 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Rubber Stamps, 1983-2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Sequitur-Log, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - SEQB12-no charge, loan review, evaluation materials sent, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Letter to Steve Wozniak, from Lee Felsenstein: Starting a Computer Revolution in the Soviet Union, 02-24-1989 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Evaluations, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Sequitur -- communications regarding distribution, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Sequitur Legal-Pacific Software, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - G. Storey, Swiftsure Data Systems, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Non-Disclosure Agreements, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Inventory, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Procedures, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Clean Up File, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Dr. Wiederhold - Letters of Reference, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Internal Documentation (Confidential), 1985 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Confidential documents, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Rationality Report, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Community Memory - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Community Memory-Letterhead (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 1.5: Financial Statements
    - Wells Fargo, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Balance Sheets and General Ledger Reports, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 33-34)
      contains 5-1/4 floppy disks
    - General Ledger Reports, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 38-40)
    - General Ledger Reports, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Form 1023 Part IV-Miscellaneous Financial Data, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - General Ledger Reports, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      contains 3-1/2 floppy disks
    - Balance Sheets and General Ledger Reports, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Wells Fargo, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Working Assets, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Balance Sheets, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 29-30)
      contains 5-1/4 and 3-1/2 disks
    - Working Assets, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Wells Fargo, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Final Moments, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      includes receipts, invoices, correspondence
    - Wells Fargo, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Working Assets, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Working Assets, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Wells Fargo, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Working Assets, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Money Market, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Wells Fargo, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - General Ledger, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Wells Fargo Checking, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 34-36)
    - Working Assets, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Wells Fargo M.M., 1991 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Ledger Entries, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Cash Disbursements, 1985-1987 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Subseries 1.6: Payroll (CLOSED UNTIL JAN.1, 2060)
    - Payroll, 1992 (Box 42)
      contains 5-1/4" floppy disks
      Closed until Jan. 1, 2060.
    - Payroll, 1991 (Box 42)
    - Payroll, 1990 (Box 42)
    - Payroll, 1996 (Box 42)
    - Payroll, 1995 (Box 42)
    - Payroll, 1994 (Box 42)
      contains 3-1/2" floppy disks
    - Payroll, 1993 (Box 42)
      contains 5-1/4" and 3-1/2" disks
    - Cash Disp Cash Receipts Payroll, 1989, 1990 (Box 42)
  - Subseries 1.7: Publications
    - The Voter; Opportunity Nocs, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Consumer Action News; Opportunity Nocs, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Box and Shipping Suppliers' Information, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Custom Labels Suppliers' Information, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Current Suppliers and Product Component Costs, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Drawings-originals, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Format sheets for layout (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Quick Reference Guide - camera ready copy (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Software Digest, vol. 2 no. 4 (comparative ratings), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 1.8: Promotional Materials
    - Sequitur-promotional materials - includes sheet of Letraset symbols, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Sequitur-promotional materials, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Sequitur-User Registration cards; Suppliers-various info and data sheets, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Sequitur promotional articles, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Photos and Articles Laundromat Terminals, Feb. 1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Homebrew Computer Club T-Shirt, Memorabilia (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Community Memory Network (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - LF-Appearances, 1988-1990 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Community Memory (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Community Memory, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - CM Press (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 1.9: Manuals
    - Software Manuals, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Materials pertaining to Sequitur (trademark of The Community Memory Project), a relational database system; quick reference guides; Also, manuals for Plib86 and Plink86 by Phoenix Software Associates, Ltd.
    - Sequitur-Reference Manual Master, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - DUMP / DIF and graphics, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - DUMP / DIF, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Freebie, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Programming Interface, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Technical Information, Sequitur 3.26 upgrade, 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      contains 5-1/4 floppy disks: Materials pertaining to Sequitur (trademark of The Community Memory Project), a relational database system.
    - Sequitur User's Guides, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Master Page Chart and Specifications for Printing IBM Manual version 3.20, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Sequitur Reference Manual version 3.30, June-Sep. 1985 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Sequitur Reference Manual version 3.30, Sep. 1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Provos manual, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 1.10: Business Records
    - Licensing Agreements, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - License Agreements (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Community Memory Project articles, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Community Memory-What is Community Memory? Forms (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Community Memory-Financials, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Community Memory-Misc., 1983 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Community Memory-Proposal, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Community Memory-Site Questions and Memos, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Community Memory-University Avenue Co-op Center Council, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Community Memory-Public Interest Computer Association (PICA), 1983 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Community Memory-news, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Community Memory-fund raising, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Community Memory-site survey forms, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Community Memory-An Introduction brochures, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Community Memory-A Public Access Information Network forms, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Community Memory-meeting minutes, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - CM-Projects (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Broadcasting (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Community Memory (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - CM Tutorial (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Relevant Data Sheets-CM (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - SPM (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Series 2: Golemics
  - Subseries 2.1: Invoices
    - Invoices, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Payables (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Paid Bills - Contract Services-R&D/Software, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 2.2: Taxes
    - Joaquin Miller and Associates-Personal Taxes, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Joaquin Miller and Associates-Personal Taxes, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Breiner and Bodian, CPAs-tax information, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Partnership-tax forms, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - CSR+D Misc Xtra Copies of $ + Tax Stuff, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - CSR+D Partners Tax Returns, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - CSR+D Partners Tax Returns, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 34-35)
    - Village Design (Exemption papers) (Golemics Taxes), 1973 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Cal Taxes, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Cal Taxes, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Cal Taxes, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Cal Taxes, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Cal Taxes, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Fed Taxes, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Fed Taxes, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Fed Taxes, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Fed Taxes, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Fed Taxes, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - State P/R Tax -- Returns, 1980-1983 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - 1099 (contract labor) filings employer copies, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - W-4s files and sent, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - California State Tax Information-Payroll, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Federal Tax Information-Payroll, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - 1099, 599, 1096 Tax Form copies, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - State Payroll Tax Returns, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - State P/R Taxes 1985-Deposits and Payment Records (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - State P/R Tax Guide-info and blank forms, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - State P/R Tax forms, office copies, payment records, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Federal P/R Tax info forms, 1980-1983 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Federal Payroll Taxes-deposit and payment records, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Federal Payroll Returns, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Sales Tax Collected-log, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - State Tax Information, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Golemics-Corporate Tax Returns, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Golemics-Corporate Tax Returns, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - State board of equalization (sales tax returns), 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Home Insurance audit, 10-25-1984 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Golemics Financial Statements, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Golemics Balance Sheets, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Office Lease-2600 Tenth Street, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Office Lease-916 Parker, 2608 Eighth Street, 1979-1984 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Bank of America auto lease, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Misc P/R Taxes, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - 1099's (1096 596), 1989 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - P/R Taxes 1987 Golemics deposits and payment records (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - P/R Taxes Golemics forms and info, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Federal P/R Taxes - Returns, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Federal P/R Taxes Deposits and Payment Records, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Federal P/R Taxes Deposits and Payment Records, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Federal P/R Taxes forms and info, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Federal P/R Taxes Returns, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - W-2 Wage and Tax Stmts W-3 Transmittals of W-2, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - W-4's Employees-Golemics, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - FUTA-Fed. Unemploy. Tax, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - State Unemployment Code + Contrib. Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - W2/W3/1099, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Golemics 1099's, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - 1099's Filed for 1986 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - W-2 Past-1979 + W-3 Transmittal for 1979 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - DE-4 W-4 Forms-Withholding Cert's Blanks and Current Completed, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - State P/R Taxes, Returns, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Taxes, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - State and Federal P/R Taxes, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - W4s, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Subseries 2.3: Correspondence
    - Correspondence-John Bourgein, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence-John Bourgein, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, Lee Felsenstein, 1983-1987 (Box 7, Folder 41)
      includes letter to Bill Gates of Microsoft
    - Correspondence, Elaina Malm, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence, Jeff K. Milstead, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence, Mimi Montgomery, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Arts of Peace, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Save Old Sols (SOS), 1980 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Messages fm Mark S., 1983 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Sequitur correspondence, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, chronological: 1980-84 Mimi Montgomery, 1980-1984 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Shahid Washeed, misc., 1984 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Jeff Milstead correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Stainless Steel embosser that marks Golemics, Incorporated, 01-01-1979 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Subseries 2.4: Financial Statements
    - Charge Receipts (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Activity-Main Checking, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - LF Old $ Records, 1976-1982 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - P/S Reconciliation of Notes to G-Copy-(G Loans to P/S), 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - P/S Reconciliation of Loans FM G-Copy, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - LGC 008-015843, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - LGC 008-012787 (Box 21, Folder 24-25)
  - Subseries 2.5: Publications
    - The Internals of the Video Graphics Terminal by Leonard Shustek: a publication of SLAC (Stanford Linear Accelerator Center), 1976 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - EFFector, 11-15-1990 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Subseries 2.6: Promotional Materials
    - Barb Article, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - Sequitur Computer Fair File, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 2.7: Manuals
    - DeSMET C88 manual (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - DMA Controller, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 57)
      includes widget
    - Flashwriter II, Users Manual by Vector Graphic, Inc., 1979 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Subseries 2.8: Business Records
    - Note issues to be resolved, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Options-J. Miller, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)